[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
‎DOCTOR X: MAFIA IN WHITE
‎EPISODE 1
‎How much does ‎tangsuyuk‎ cost these days?
‎How will you ever pay off your debt
‎and live independently at this rate?
‎Yes!
‎That's how you do it!
‎I don't know how to lose.
‎Man, she's so damn loud.
‎Hey, mister. Change out the lights!
‎Want to go against her? ‎I'll clean her out, down to her underwear.
‎Man, even I can't wear something that big.
‎Sir, can we get ‎tangsuyuk‎ and ‎jjajangmyeon‎?
‎Fine.
‎Make those extra-large!
‎Goodness, a doctor-turned-mayor.
‎As head of the Seonam Medical Association, ‎I'm thrilled, Mr. Mayor.
‎This is all thanks to you, President Kim.
‎Not at all.
‎My dear Mr. Mayor, ‎I hope you won't forget me,
‎Director Kim Myeong-seop, ‎and Guseo University Medical Center too.
‎I could never forget you, Director.
‎Congratulations, Mr. Mayor.
‎Thank you.
‎Gosh, why are you pouring wine like soju?
‎You're sure in a celebratory mood.
‎-Mayor Im Ho-seok. ‎-Yes?
‎This is Dr. Do Yun-sik from GUMC.
‎Oh, yes. I enjoyed your latest paper.
‎Your clinical research is exceptional.
‎It's all thanks to Director Kim ‎and Chairman Gu.
‎-Pour me a glass. ‎-Yes, sir.
‎-Not too much. ‎-Yes, sir.
‎-Chairman Gu, I'm Jung Geon-hui. ‎-Right.
‎Chairman Gu, I'm Kim Gwang-hyeon.
‎Okay.
‎-Sir, I'm Lee Gyeong-seok. ‎-All right.
‎Go into plastics or dermatology. ‎Why general surgery?
‎-Or how about ophthalmology? ‎-Let him be.
‎It's good to know a surgeon ‎when you get older.
‎So how about orthopedics?
‎In that case, why not internal medicine?
‎I didn't go to med school for you guys.
‎Right. ‎You went to inherit the family practice.
‎Just shoot some pool, you punks.
‎Crazy bastard. What are you, a pervert?
‎I grazed it with the cue stick earlier.
‎I need to go to the restroom.
‎Hurry up.
‎-What's wrong? Hey! ‎-It hurts!
‎Sir, are you okay?
‎Where does it hurt?
‎Right here.
‎Is it swollen? What is this part called?
‎Are you a doctor too?
‎I… I'm an intern.
‎Get him up. Now.
‎Okay.
‎It hurts.
‎I'm going to have to undress you.
‎Lady, are you insane?
‎-You want your friend to die? ‎-Damn it.
‎Cough for me.
‎Tighten your stomach.
‎Cough.
‎It's a left inguinal hernia. ‎I performed a manual reduction.
‎Oh, an inguinal hernia…
‎There's a risk of recurrence. ‎He needs emergency surgery.
‎You're a doctor, right? Come with us.
‎But I'm an intern.
‎Wait a minute!
‎Can I at least get your name?
‎We fought through the COVID-19 pandemic,
‎the CCTV mandate in operating rooms,
‎and strikes over medical school quotas.
‎We've managed to endure
‎this grueling ordeal ‎with everything we had.
‎But the crisis isn't over.
‎We face union struggles from within,
‎Medical Service Act reforms ‎from the outside,
‎and the media paints us as frauds.
‎Protecting doctors is the only way
‎to set healthcare right, but those…
‎Those fools fail to see it.
‎Now more than ever,
‎Magnolia must unite.
‎The election ‎of our very own Mayor Im Ho-seok
‎is just the beginning.
‎Well said, sir!
‎All right.
‎I swear before the white coat
‎never to forget where I started.
‎And I'll never forget
‎the proactive support from Magnolia!
‎Everyone,
‎here's to the white coat!
‎-Cheers! ‎-Cheers!
‎Yet another resignation?
‎I'm going to lose it.
‎They're not answering?
‎Hey, let's talk more later.
‎Why did you come out?
‎You work too hard.
‎No, please go back inside.
‎I need to use the restroom.
‎No more wine, sir.
‎You should be protecting patients, ‎you goddamn bastards.
‎I hope you all get gout ‎after eating all that meat.
‎Is there even a doctor worth protecting?
‎You bastards.
‎Wow, this is insane.
‎I've never taken someone to the ER ‎after a manual reduction.
‎I've never seen this before either.
‎Wait a minute!
‎Can I at least get your name?
‎What?
‎What's that?
‎What does that mean?
‎Who are you?
‎The white tower is collapsing.
‎Through the COVID-19 pandemic, ‎the CCTV mandate in operating rooms,
‎and the strikes over med school quotas,
‎hospitals faced constant turmoil.
‎SURGERY-RELATED DEPARTMENTS ‎WILL SHARE STAFF ROOM
‎They started construction a while ago.
‎But I don't see any progress.
‎Damn it.
‎The government pushed ‎a half-baked bill for show,
‎and doctors responded by walking out.
‎As the conflict intensifies, ‎patients are overlooked.
‎First doctors, and now nurses?
‎I know working in surgery is grueling,
‎but how did you let this happen?
‎-Sorry, sir. ‎-I'm sorry.
‎I'm making rounds ‎for the first time in ages.
‎I'm going to lose face over this.
‎What about the OR?
‎Well…
‎I did find someone on short notice
‎to help out temporarily…
‎GUSEO UNIVERSITY SEONAM MEDICAL CENTER
‎Then…
‎a new kind of doctor appeared.
‎One who belongs to no group.
‎Hello, I'm your new surgical intern!
‎My name is Park Tae-gyeong!
‎I'm excited to work with you!
‎Excuse me, am I late?
‎No, I'm not.
‎Sir, can I ask you a question?
‎Hi, I'm Ma Seong-gyu, ‎your senior resident.
‎Nice to meet you.
‎I should be nicer to you, ‎but I don't have the capability
‎because the director just called rounds,
‎which means you need to ‎get out there right now.
‎You can sit…
‎Not that you'd choose general surgery…
‎Just sit wherever.
‎But don't quit this week.
‎-What are you doing, intern? ‎-What?
‎Oh, rounds.
‎Yes, sir!
‎Director Kim Myeong-seop ‎will now begin rounds.
‎A freelancer unattached ‎to any hospital department.
‎Also known as a mercenary doctor.
‎This is the story of a lone wolf.
‎A solitary figure that has emerged ‎in the era of mafia in white,
‎where even the practice of saving lives ‎is driven by money and power.
‎This person right here
‎despises authority and answers to no one.
‎Her only weapons are her medical license
‎and the surgical skills ‎she has honed from the bottom up.
‎Meet Gye Su-jeong, a surgeon.
‎Also known as
‎Doctor X.
‎I haven't had a chance ‎to look at your file yet.
‎What's your name?
‎Gye Su-jeong.
‎Your last name is "Gye"? That's unusual.
‎There's a pre-op conference today,
‎so attend that first.
‎You…
‎Dr. Gye.
‎You need to verbally respond ‎when he talks to you.
‎-Director Kim is waiting. Please hurry. ‎-Oh my.
‎Director Kim seems really pumped.
‎He's even leading this conference.
‎He gets to perform surgery ‎right before his retirement,
‎so I think he's excited.
‎Everyone, rise.
‎THE 7TH MEDICAL STAFF CONFERENCE
‎Please be seated.
‎We will now begin the conference.
‎The patient is an 80-year-old male, ‎Seo Byeong-gyu.
‎He's scheduled for an open cholecystectomy ‎due to suspected gallbladder cancer.
‎Per the patient's strong request,
‎Director Kim Myeong-seop ‎will personally perform the surgery.
‎The surgical technique ‎is the MS Technique,
‎which was developed by Director Kim.
‎This is a chance to see ‎a legendary yet fundamental technique
‎refined over the course of 30 years.
‎"MS Technique"? It's just a laparotomy.
‎This will be my last chance ‎to reflect on being a surgeon.
‎Don't say that, sir.
‎As always,
‎I'll do my best for the patient.
‎Please allow Dr. Bae Heung-gon ‎and Dr. Ma Seong-gyu to assist you.
‎I look forward to learning from you.
‎Aside from these two,
‎I'd like anyone else who is free ‎to observe as well.
‎-Thank you. ‎-Thank you.
‎Objection.
‎Who's that?
‎Is that the temporary worker ‎sent by the locum tenens agency?
‎Their absolute ace?
‎Temporary worker? Ace?
‎What do you mean?
‎Good. Our intern knows a thing or two.
‎Absolute ace, my foot.
‎"X" is more like it.
‎Do we really need to
‎open him up?
‎Why open surgery?
‎Laparoscopic cholecystectomy ‎has long been the standard
‎for quick recovery and stable outcomes.
‎Open surgery demands ‎at least a ten-day hospital stay
‎and takes a huge toll on the patient.
‎So why do you insist on doing it?
‎I'm sorry, Director Kim.
‎She's the locum who just came…
‎You rely on machines a lot, right?
‎That's good too.
‎Dr. Bae here knows it better than anyone
‎since he is renowned ‎as a specialist in laparoscopy.
‎This patient is a very fortunate case,
‎as his condition was caught ‎on a routine ultrasound
‎before any symptoms developed.
‎But it's not easy to distinguish
‎between inflammation ‎and gallbladder cancer on imaging.
‎Given the risk of tumor metastasis,
‎any suspicion of gallbladder cancer ‎warrants open surgery.
‎Rather than insisting on ‎a minimally invasive approach,
‎a case like this requires open surgery.
‎Don't you agree, Dr. Bae?
‎Yes, sir.
‎A lap chole has several disadvantages ‎compared to open surgery
‎for early-stage gallbladder cancer--
‎Given that this is a very fortunate case
‎caught before any symptoms developed,
‎early detection of gallbladder cancer ‎means high survival rates,
‎so we should choose a surgery ‎that prioritizes the patient's condition.
‎He's an 80-year-old elderly man.
‎He also developed ‎post-COVID pneumonia three years ago.
‎Remove it laparoscopically ‎and do a biopsy.
‎Depending on the results,
‎we can perform open surgery ‎as a next step.
‎She knows her stuff.
‎A real surgeon must be able to
‎directly visualize ‎and palpate the surgical site
‎to handle any bleeding or adhesions.
‎They must excise ‎the source of the patient's condition
‎as deeply and widely as possible ‎to ensure their safety.
‎This is the best way
‎to save a patient's life!
‎-You're absolutely right, sir! ‎-Yes, you are.
‎It seems like…
‎you're just excited to get a booking ‎after a million years.
‎What? "Get a booking"?
‎Where's your sense of respect ‎for the director?
‎Then instead of "get a booking," ‎how about…
‎Get a reservation?
‎"Reservation"?
‎How dare you say the director ‎"got a reservation"?
‎Just be honest.
‎You're eager to take on the case ‎after a long break,
‎but you don't know ‎how to do a laparoscopy.
‎So you're just stringing together
‎a bunch of outdated theories ‎to cover that up.
‎If these people in white coats
‎actually have medical licenses,
‎they'll agree the laparoscopic specialist ‎over there should do it.
‎I bet that specialist ‎is thinking the same thing.
‎Me? That's not true!
‎That's not what I think at all, sir.
‎What kind of nonsense are you saying?
‎Well…
‎You're big on showing proper respect…
‎I know.
‎This seems appropriate.
‎You show excessive greed in your old age.
‎Get out!
‎What are you doing? Get her out!
‎You…
‎I'm sorry, Director.
‎Please sit down, sir.
‎Yes, please take a seat.
‎Goodness.
‎She's so cool.
‎Ms. Jang.
‎About that mad dog you sent over…
‎I mean, that mad doc…
‎I mean, that crazy Dr. Gye Su-jeong.
‎What's wrong with her?
‎Goodness, is that so?
‎It seems Dr. Gye behaved inappropriately.
‎DIRECTOR JANG'S LOCUM TENENS AGENCY
‎I'm sorry about that.
‎Dr. Gye has quite a mouth on her.
‎SU-JEONG, FEB. 9: FIRST DAY AT GUMC
‎But her skills are undeniable,
‎so she'll be a great asset ‎to the hospital.
‎I'll take this into consideration
‎and charge less for the first month.
‎Of course, I'll make sure ‎she gets her act together.
‎Yes.
‎Thank you. Goodbye.
‎-Is it my turn? ‎-Did she get into trouble?
‎She just said her piece.
‎Here we go.
‎I need shoulder acupuncture before you go.
‎-Will you pay me in advance? ‎-I'll even cook for you.
‎You'll cook for me?
‎-Wow, you sure? ‎-One, two, three, four, five.
‎Landed on Seoul.
‎No, not Seoul…
‎When I heard ‎it could be gallbladder cancer,
‎my mind went blank.
‎Then I remembered seeing you on TV ‎a long time ago.
‎After watching the show,
‎I realized that gallbladder cancer ‎was very dangerous.
‎Yes, well…
‎The DBS medical documentary ‎Secrets of Life and Death‎ introduced
‎Dr. Kim Myeong-Seop here ‎as the god of gallbladder cancer.
‎It's such an honor for us.
‎Actually, I've supplied surgical gloves
‎to this hospital for over 20 years.
‎I supply other hospitals as well,
‎but I take great pride in this place--
‎-Right, please sign here. ‎-Okay.
‎-Director Kim has another appointment. ‎-Oh, I'm sorry.
‎By the way…
‎It's nothing much, ‎but this is for you.
‎I'll get in big trouble if I accept this.
‎No, please take it.
‎It'll make us feel better if you do.
‎We insist.
‎-Please take it, Director. ‎-Goodness.
‎Thank you.
‎Sir, the update is almost done.
‎Do you need anything else?
‎I'm fine.
‎-You can leave after it's done. ‎-Yes, sir.
‎Good grief.
‎It's all updated, sir.
‎Get rid of this.
‎-And empty the trash. ‎-Yes. Thank you, sir.
‎"Thank you, sir"?
‎Why did I thank him?
‎What's that?
‎It's ‎jocheong‎.
‎Jocheong‎? Like that rich honey?
‎It's homemade. ‎The store-bought kind isn't this color.
‎How do you know that?
‎My grandmother always made me some ‎for the holidays.
‎And she made some for good luck ‎when I took the college entrance exam.
‎She was going to make some ‎for my medical licensing exam,
‎but she passed away two years ago.
‎Then you can have it.
‎You have to stir the pot all night ‎just to make this much.
‎At least try a spoonful.
‎She must've worked so hard.
‎I'm sure she made it ‎with genuine gratitude.
‎You're the sentimental type, aren't you?
‎What?
‎Never mind. Take good care of them.
‎Yes, sir.
‎RESUME
‎Let's just fire her right now.
‎She's so damn disrespectful.
‎I got the signed consent form ‎and updated the director's computer.
‎Good work.
‎Come on, Dr. Do.
‎Hey.
‎Read this.
‎"Gye Su-jeong."
‎Her name is Gye Su-jeong?
‎Man, she's older than I thought.
‎Medical school at Cubanacan University
‎and the University of Florida.
‎Below that.
‎"Returned to Korea after volunteering ‎in remote medical missions worldwide."
‎"General surgery. Cardiothoracic surgery."
‎She's got some skills for her age.
‎That's so cool.
‎Hey.
‎Dr. Bae is double-board certified ‎in neurosurgery and general.
‎"Registered as a surgical locum ‎at the Jang Hui-suk Locum Tenens Agency."
‎"Hobbies, surgery."
‎"Special skills, surgery."
‎It's all surgery.
‎Seems like a scam artist.
‎-We're keeping her on? ‎-Look into her, sir.
‎Why would she come here with this resume?
‎What do you mean? ‎What's wrong with our hospital?
‎That's not what I meant, sir.
‎Hey. You…
‎For now, you'll assist Dr. Ma Seong-gyu ‎and Dr. Park Tae-gyeong.
‎Please.
‎Assist them with what?
‎What else?
‎Just follow these two around.
‎Let's prep for the conference.
‎Get going.
‎Now what?
‎We're short on staff, ‎so we'll try her out for a week.
‎It's free.
‎Keep her glued to her desk ‎and away from Director Kim.
‎SEO BYEONG-GYU, M/80 ‎OPERATES A RUBBER FACTORY
‎Excuse me.
‎The inguinal hernia…
‎Do you remember me from the pool hall?
‎Your diagnosis was spot on,
‎and he went straight into surgery.
‎By the way…
‎what does this mean?
‎When do people draw an "X"?
‎Well, I guess to say…
‎"That's not it" or "That won't do"?
‎There you go.
‎"You're…
‎not it."
‎"You're not good enough"?
‎You don't think I'm good enough?
‎Why not? Why do I get an "X"?
‎I never told you to look at ‎Mr. Seo Byeong-gyu's chart.
‎He runs a rubber factory.
‎Yes, and he also supplies ‎surgical gloves here.
‎-He seemed very proud of it. ‎-Just do the work I gave you.
‎Would you want Director Kim ‎to operate on you?
‎What?
‎You're a doctor, ‎so you know this is unnecessary.
‎That was all settled at the conference.
‎Would you want him to?
‎-Of course. ‎-Then…
‎what about your parents?
‎Not you, but your mother.
‎That's an extreme scenario--
‎This patient has a child too.
‎They're just not a doctor.
‎I'd want him to.
‎I'd want Director Kim ‎to operate on my mother for me.
‎And if I were that patient's child,
‎he'd most definitely have ‎Director Kim as his surgeon
‎for the sake of my future.
‎I need you to revise this ‎and send it back to me.
‎-Yes, sir. ‎-Good.
‎-What's going on? ‎-I'm so glad you're here, Dr. Bae.
‎This is why I don't like you people.
‎What did she just say?
‎"You people"?
‎-No, sir. You misheard her. ‎-He heard me right.
‎-Hey. ‎-I said…
‎I don't like you people.
‎People who only studied ‎to get rich and climb the ladder.
‎People with no ethics, no beliefs,
‎and no independent thought, ‎who are smart yet stupid.
‎You grovel to superiors
‎while lording it over patients.
‎You suck up to superiors and bully nurses.
‎You ignore corruption at the top ‎and blame the system for your own mess.
‎You irresponsible people ‎care only for your own comfort,
‎so you leave surgery to an old man
‎who neglects his health and skills ‎and is lucky if his hands don't shake.
‎You're really pushing it.
‎You know full well ‎how much the patient will suffer
‎with his life on the line,
‎yet you only think about ‎how to get off the hook,
‎complacent as ever.
‎You expect patients
‎who are much older than you ‎to bow at the waist and say,
‎"Please save me" and "Thank you."
‎You people…
‎are merely doctors by name.
‎Wow.
‎You are the worst.
‎Have you lost your mind?
‎-Get out. ‎-Get out.
‎-Get the hell out. ‎-Out!
‎What are you looking at? Want to fight?
‎Come on. Let's see what you've got.
‎Come at me. I dare you.
‎What's that for? ‎Are you going to hit me with it?
‎Six o'clock!
‎That's right.
‎-Just leave. ‎-Oh.
‎"Oh"?
‎What? Don't tell me…
‎She clocked out?
‎Go and bring her back.
‎-Yes, sir. ‎-Right now.
‎How dare she clock out?
‎SEO ******-GYU
‎I knew it.
‎It was a good idea ‎to have Director Kim operate,
‎seeing the doctors ‎taking turns to check up on us.
‎-Someone else was here? ‎-Yes.
‎They were just here.
‎Here.
‎Have some mango too.
‎Our daughter bought some ‎from the department store
‎to cheer up her sick dad,
‎since he'll need to fast soon.
‎It's very sweet.
‎The other doctor really enjoyed it.
‎You gave them some yogurt too, right?
‎Of course.
‎By the way, they're a doctor, right?
‎Did you catch their name?
‎They weren't wearing a white coat,
‎but said they were a doctor.
‎-Was it a woman? ‎-Yes.
‎She did say something odd.
‎She suggested pushing back the surgery.
‎Everything is okay ‎with Director Kim, right?
‎Of course. Did she say anything else?
‎When I told her ‎I couldn't postpone because of my factory,
‎she asked if I'd like a different surgeon.
‎I told her absolutely not
‎and insisted on getting surgery ‎from the director.
‎She was probably just asking.
‎I'm sure tomorrow's surgery will go well.
‎Oh, yes.
‎Thank you.
‎Thank you for this.
‎-Of course. ‎-Get some rest.
‎-Try this first. ‎-Still,
‎it's the largest hub hospital ‎in the suburbs of Seoul.
‎But there's less meddling than in Seoul,
‎so they're shadier, ‎leaving us with lots of ways to profit.
‎It's good for us.
‎-Good for you, you mean. ‎-What?
‎Su-jeong.
‎Breathe. Don't inhale your food.
‎Take shorter showers. ‎The gas bill went up.
‎But I pay my bills.
‎That director…
‎Who? Kim Myeong-seop?
‎You know anything about him?
‎Can't tell you for free. ‎I'll dock your pay.
‎Jeez, you're savage.
‎Here, eat up.
‎Gosh, who cooked this?
‎I should've come sooner, Director Kim.
‎Skip the pleasantries.
‎We normally only give this ‎after signing a contract,
‎but please accept this with our apologies.
‎Is this the famous melon gift ‎that represents your agency?
‎I appreciate you recognizing it.
‎-I left the contents with the secretary. ‎-You did?
‎You know you have to keep the box, right?
‎Oh, right.
‎The melon looks delicious.
‎This is a top-grade melon.
‎It's from overseas and hard to get.
‎Really?
‎Dr. Gye lived overseas for a long time,
‎so she's not familiar ‎with Korean medical culture.
‎She wasn't aware of ‎your outstanding legacy,
‎so please forgive her.
‎All right.
‎Dr. Gye has many shortcomings.
‎Just give her some scut work ‎and keep her around.
‎She just doesn't know any better.
‎I'd like to observe your surgery, sir.
‎Oh, really?
‎Yes. I'd like to see you f…
‎I mean, see you demonstrate ‎the MS Technique.
‎All right.
‎You can observe.
‎Thank you.
‎He hasn't performed surgery in a while,
‎and all eyes will be on him.
‎I'll cover for him.
‎Without him knowing, got it?
‎Yes, of course.
‎Where's Dr. Gye?
‎Why ask that before surgery and jinx it?
‎I didn't know that would jinx it.
‎You always get the last word.
‎I'll let you have the last word next time.
‎You little punk.
‎Dr. Bu, you made it.
‎Director Kim said he invited you.
‎It's been a while.
‎It's so nice to see you here.
‎How do you like it over there?
‎I'm just doing my best.
‎You're here.
‎Goodness.
‎Dr. Bu came to watch ‎Director Kim and his miracle hands, huh?
‎He was in line to become director ‎at the main hospital,
‎but he got pushed out
‎and is now working at the southern branch.
‎Oh my, I see.
‎But why did he get pushed out?
‎He's no fun to be around,
‎and he's the very model ‎of a devoted doctor.
‎It's no wonder ‎other doctors can't stand him.
‎I see.
‎He's no fun in more ways than one.
‎No, bring me powdered gloves.
‎-Excuse me? ‎-These make my hands sweaty.
‎We have some ready, sir.
‎Right.
‎The induction was uneventful,
‎and his vitals are stable.
‎We're finally recording ‎this legendary surgery.
‎I never knew that CCTV ‎had a purpose until today.
‎No need to be nervous.
‎I'll do what I always do.
‎Very nice, Dr. Bae.
‎I used to listen to this
‎and remove two gallbladders at once ‎using my technique.
‎Turn up the volume.
‎I can't hear the monitor.
‎Turn it down.
‎Let's begin.
‎Director Kim Myeong-seop's cholecystectomy
‎for Mr. Seo Byeong-gyu will now begin.
‎-Let's do a good job. ‎-Let's do a good job.
‎Scalpel.
‎I warned them ‎not to offer the scalpel first.
‎Doesn't it make things easier ‎when they take the initiative?
‎It's his way of saying,
‎"You're just a nurse. How dare you?"
‎He made a lot of nurses cry.
‎What an ass.
‎An asset.
‎He's a good asset.
‎You should stop the surgery ‎and take him in for an MRI.
‎Why do an MRI for the patient?
‎Not the patient. Director Kim.
‎What kind of nonsense is that?
‎Want to get kicked out?
‎Oh my, Dr. Gye is talking crap again.
‎Come over here, Dr. Gye.
‎Be quiet.
‎This should be fun.
‎Who turned the volume down?
‎Hurry up. Sponge.
‎MS forceps.
‎These custom forceps were designed
‎for the technique named after me.
‎I used to do at least ‎four surgeries a day with these.
‎That's amazing, sir.
‎I'll give these to you after this surgery.
‎I'd be honored, sir.
‎Experienced surgeons normally do
‎ten cases a day.
‎He's slow as hell.
‎Wipe.
‎Look at this.
‎Recurrent inflammation ‎has caused severe adhesions.
‎Opening him up was the right call.
‎MS forceps.
‎Look at how elegantly it grabs hold.
‎Right angle.
‎What are you doing? ‎There's sweat in my eyes.
‎Metz.
‎BP dropping. Systolic's under 60. ‎Heart rate's over 150.
‎Vitals are unstable.
‎Patient's in shock. Pushing a bolus.
‎-Director Kim? ‎-Director, how…
‎Sir?
‎You need to raise your mask.
‎-Sir? ‎-Director Kim?
‎-Director? ‎-Your mask, sir.
‎Sir, are you okay?
‎What's happening?
‎Director Kim, wake up.
‎Sir, are you with me?
‎Squeeze my hand, sir.
‎-What's going on? ‎-Mental status is declining.
‎It looks like left-sided hemiplegia!
‎CVA, likely an ischemic stroke.
‎-Run a CT. ‎-Bring a stretcher!
‎Vitals are unstable. ‎We risk contamination, so clear out now!
‎Secure an IV line ‎and start fluids for Director Kim, now.
‎Call neurosurgery!
‎Wait, have Dr. Bae stay with him!
‎-I'll be right there! ‎-Okay!
‎One, two.
‎What about this patient? He's in shock!
‎Get in here!
‎What about this patient?
‎Dr. Bae! Dr. Ma!
‎-Hurry up. ‎-You can't all leave!
‎What about the patient?
‎Stay here for now and watch him.
‎What? Where are you going, Dr. Bae?
‎Ma Seong-gyu!
‎Hey!
‎Dr. Jo, what do we do?
‎I'm keeping his vitals stable. ‎Page someone.
‎Everyone who wasn't in surgery
‎was here, but they left.
‎There's no one to page.
‎It doesn't matter. Call anyone.
‎Should I try?
‎What?
‎This patient is alone ‎and fighting for his life.
‎I have to try something…
‎But there are too many instruments.
‎You're an intern, you idiot!
‎Call a resident right now!
‎But there's no one available…
‎There ‎is‎ someone.
‎Vitals?
‎Can't get a BP. Heart rate is 170.
‎All right.
‎Everyone, put your hands up.
‎I brought what you asked for.
‎Everyone switch to those gloves ‎and change into new scrubs.
‎Let's max out the room air exchange.
‎-Push epi and dex. ‎-Got it.
‎You'll assist.
‎Okay.
‎The alarms stopped.
‎Turn off the music.
‎BP's 120 over 65.
‎Heart rate is 90.
‎Resuming surgery.
‎Tie 2-0 silk.
‎Off.
‎Scissors.
‎Tie.
‎Off.
‎Sponge forceps.
‎Hold this.
‎Forceps.
‎Right angle.
‎Pass me whatever you think I'll need next. ‎I'll ask if I need something else.
‎Yes, Doctor.
‎Cystic duct ligation.
‎She has quick hands, doesn't she?
‎I'm the head of the country's ‎first-ever locum tenens agency.
‎My name is Jang Hui-suk.
‎DIRECTOR JANG HUI-SUK ‎LOCUM TENENS AGENCY
‎And that's our agency's star surgeon,
‎Dr. Gye Su-jeong.
‎Specimen's out. Send it to pathology.
‎Gauze count?
‎All gauze accounted for.
‎Let's close up.
‎OPERATION TIME, TIME, ANESTHESIA TIME
‎Estimated blood loss?
‎-200 cc. ‎-Before the patient wakes, let's push--
‎Pushing 100 mg of hydrocortisone.
‎We're finished here.
‎Dr. Gye?
‎Thank you for your hard work.
‎Thank you.
‎Thank you!
‎Oh my goodness. You're still here, Dr. Bu?
‎I left my phone here.
‎I'm all over the place.
‎Director Kim pulled through.
‎Our neurosurgery team and Dr. Bae ‎did excellent work.
‎That's good to hear.
‎But that crazy doctor…
‎How on earth did she know?
‎Have you lost your mind?
‎What did you give him?
‎Dr. Bae, he's breathing.
‎Move fast and restore blood flow.
‎DIRECTOR JANG HUI-SUK ‎LOCUM TENENS AGENCY
‎Dr. Gye!
‎So Dr. Gye performed the surgery?
‎Did you page her?
‎Are you reprimanding Dr. Park?
‎The bigger issue ‎was that no one was there.
‎It was an emergency situation,
‎and we ended up ‎with another patient on our hands--
‎And it mattered more ‎because it was the director, right?
‎How could you leave a patient like that?
‎So should we have abandoned him?
‎Director Kim is a patient too.
‎You should've secured ‎a primary surgeon first!
‎What are you doing?
‎Put that down right now.
‎Dr. Gye.
‎You performed that surgery ‎without permission.
‎You just saw Mr. Seo go into shock ‎from an unknown cause.
‎"Unknown cause"?
‎You know the cause.
‎Come on, admit it.
‎Will you answer…
‎Stop. Just stop!
‎Stop eating!
‎Here.
‎Here and here. You're all doctors here.
‎Look for it.
‎That injection.
‎It was epinephrine, right?
‎EPINEPHRINE: ‎TREATMENT FOR ALLERGIC REACTIONS
‎Why won't you answer?
‎Me?
‎What?
‎Why are you staring at me?
‎Six o'clock!
‎Again?
‎A clock was behind me again?
‎-Go and catch her. ‎-Yes, sir.
‎Epinephrine?
‎But Director Kim had an ischemic stroke.
‎In the observation gallery,
‎Dr. Gye said to do an MRI on him.
‎What?
‎I think she knew he was going to collapse.
‎SEO ******-GYU
‎I'm not catching anyone.
‎Just go home, Dr. Gye.
‎GUSEO UNIVERSITY SEONAM MEDICAL CENTER
‎Dr. Do.
‎Yes?
‎Did Dr. Gye perform the surgery?
‎He's asking if you performed the surgery.
‎There you go again.
‎Yes?
‎Tell her she did a good job.
‎As expected, doing a laparotomy ‎with the MS Technique
‎was the right move.
‎Yes, sir.
‎He says, "Good job."
‎"As expected, doing a laparotomy ‎with the MS Technique was the right move."
‎No. As expected, ‎you shouldn't have opened him up.
‎If there's nothing else, please excuse me.
‎Dr. Gye.
‎Tell her I'm firing her.
‎What a nutjob.
‎"You're fired, you nutjob,"
‎is what he says.
‎What's a doctor ‎who doesn't like doctors doing here?
‎I just got fired.
‎I'm going home.
‎What? She got fired?
‎Ms. Han.
‎But she saved a life. How could he--
‎-Dr. Park. ‎-Forget it. Let's just eat.
‎We said we'd be right back.
‎Any experienced doctor ‎could do what she did.
‎You're so right, Dr. Bae.
‎One of my professors
‎accidentally played a surgical video ‎at 1.5 times normal speed in class.
‎Everyone laughed then.
‎But…
‎It's not funny if you're faster than that.
‎Hey, you haven't seen enough surgeries.
‎I could pull off a procedure like that ‎at that speed.
‎Really?
‎At that speed?
‎You didn't watch ‎the video carefully, did you?
‎You wouldn't know we switched gloves.
‎I was called out because of them.
‎She said to bring non-latex gloves.
‎-Latex allergy? ‎-Latex allergy?
‎Anaphylaxis.
‎How did she know?
‎His pre-op form ‎didn't mention a latex allergy.
‎Rubber factory.
‎But long-term rubber exposure ‎doesn't always lead to a delayed allergy--
‎There was a strong enough allergen ‎to trigger a reaction.
‎Wait a minute. So how did she know?
‎How did she know ‎he was going to have a stroke?
‎You don't think…
‎she slipped him a drug, do you?
‎Stop talking nonsense and just eat.
‎She's gone now.
‎The doctor saying irrational things ‎about drugging people keeps his job,
‎while the one who saved a life gets fired.
‎This hospital is a circus.
‎That's enough. ‎We're hanging by a thread as it is.
‎I also can't eat
‎anything like this because of allergies.
‎I'm relieved you're okay, Director Kim.
‎So you saw it all, huh?
‎Yes, I saw the whole thing.
‎I was very concerned.
‎No one seemed to know
‎you went into anaphylactic shock.
‎Anaphylaxis?
‎How did you know?
‎I stopped by your office ‎to say hello this morning,
‎and saw your secretary ‎throw away some melon.
‎And you kept scratching ‎the back of your neck in the OR.
‎I'm sure you know
‎delayed allergic reactions to latex ‎are common among healthcare workers.
‎Latex?
‎Director Kim.
‎Why did you do it?
‎Powdered gloves were banned by law
‎because inhaling the particles ‎can cause anaphylactic shock.
‎But you ignored that ‎for your own convenience.
‎Your patient's life was at stake.
‎No. I didn't--
‎Of course, you didn't know.
‎You didn't know that both you ‎and the patient had a latex allergy.
‎Or that something ‎would trigger a reaction.
‎How long have you been away from the OR
‎not to know that?
‎No, it's not in the footage.
‎However…
‎I have this.
‎MAY EXACERBATE ‎LATEX-INDUCED ALLERGIC REACTIONS
‎I heard you also received a box ‎from the locum tenens agency.
‎Since the hospital pays ‎for temporary workers anyway,
‎you got to line your own pockets ‎without spending a dime.
‎I know, I know.
‎Just breathe.
‎I only want…
‎one thing.
‎Thank you.
‎Thank you, Doctor.
‎THE DIRECTOR WILL BE MAKING ROUNDS ‎PLEASE GET READY
‎Director Bu Seung-gwon ‎will now begin rounds.
‎Hello.
‎DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
‎I appreciate you requesting ‎Dr. Gye Su-jeong.
‎Thank you.
‎Director.
‎Here is the new contract.
‎Just a moment.
‎EMPLOYMENT CONTRACT
‎Oh my.
‎Eight-hour workdays.
‎Overtime comes with special pay.
‎Surgeries come with per-case bonuses.
‎Double pay for night shifts.
‎Here's the rate sheet.
‎Bonuses?
‎Wait…
‎This is higher than my salary.
‎I can't accept this, sir.
‎Why don't you join our agency then?
‎Sir, if anything goes wrong ‎during surgery,
‎it'll be entirely on us.
‎Dr. Gye here will not do any work ‎that doesn't require
‎a medical license.
‎There's a lot of scut work ‎to do in hospitals.
‎-That's why she-- ‎-Enough.
‎For example, helping attendings ‎with their research.
‎I don't do that.
‎Pulling data for attendings.
‎Director rounds, attending rounds.
‎I don't do that.
‎Work dinners, networking, ‎gatherings, making friendly overtures,
‎talent shows, and more.
‎I don't do any of that.
‎It's all written there.
‎SPECIAL TERMS
‎I don't do any of that
‎for any reason.
‎What is this nonsense?
‎What's important is that Dr. Gye…
‎Failure?
‎I don't do that either.
‎Director.
‎You start today.
‎Thank you. You won't regret this.
‎I look forward to ‎working with you, Dr. Gye.
‎I don't do social niceties either.
‎Why that…
‎Did you put what I gave you to good use?
‎Yes.
‎Then we'll save that for next time.
‎Have a good day, everyone.
‎If you ever
‎Become lonely
‎Oh, wait.
‎Just a minute!
‎That person won't help you ‎build the future you want.
‎She has an impressive resume.
‎She'll be an asset to the hospital.
‎But there are others with her experience--
‎Did you watch the entire surgical video?
‎Yes.
‎I've never seen hands move that fast.
‎There's someone else who should have this.
‎Why are they bringing in that mad dog?
‎This is insane.
‎She hates belonging to a group ‎and despises authority.
‎This person…
‎could throw everything into turmoil.
‎RESUME ‎NAME: GYE SU-JEONG
‎Dr. Gye Su-jeong!
‎Oh, here.
‎I noticed your name ‎wasn't embroidered on it yet.
‎Oh, and I know about ‎melons and tropical fruit.
‎People with latex allergies ‎can react to tropical fruit too.
‎He runs a rubber factory.
‎No, bring me powdered gloves.
‎Her only weapons are her medical license
‎and the surgical skills ‎she has honed from the bottom up.
‎Dr. Gye Su-jeong!
‎Gye Su-jeong.
‎Will you answer for once?
‎Did you hear me?
‎Are you ignoring us?
‎Hey, Gye-snake!
‎Gye Su-jeong, the surgeon.
‎At the end of the day, she's disposable.
‎We can cut her loose ‎along with the hospital's other problems.
‎So let's just wait and see how she does.
‎Why did you come back ‎if you hate it so much?
‎Why did you become a doctor ‎if you hate it so much?
‎Also known as
‎Doctor X.
‎IN MEMORY OF KIM HYUN-I, ‎OUR CHERISHED COLLEAGUE
‎DOCTOR X: MAFIA IN WHITE
‎-"Mad dog"? ‎-‎You can't do it with your skills.
‎Are we really working with her?
‎She gets on my nerves.
‎Can I just not do the surgery?
‎-Objection. ‎-Are you saying you can do it?
‎Just let me die!
‎There's no difference ‎if you die today or next week.
‎She'll push ahead with surgery ‎no matter the risk to the patient.
‎Now it's starting to get fun.
‎You're bound to fail at some point.
‎You're a doctor!
‎You have a duty to save your patient!
‎Subtitle translation by: Jenny Kim